Guide to the Douglas C. Engelbart Papers M0638
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3. Media
  - Subseries 3.5 Miscellaneous film & video
    - SRI/AHI Software Bootstrap film, 1969-01-21 (Box 3 (misc), Object 7)
    - SRI unidentifed film ["reel somehow came into possession of WJE, '83"], 1969-01-21 (Box 4 (misc), Object 1)
    - Engelbart Edited from 3 Reel, 90 Minute, 1969 (Box 4 (misc), Object 2)
  - Subseries 3.6. Bootstrap Seminars, Bush Symposium, Unfinished Revolution copies
    - Bush Symposium 1-11 (11 DVDs) (Box 2 (Misc))
    - Bootstrap Seminar Day 2, Sessions 1-4 (4 DVDs), 1990-06-20 (Box 2 (Misc))
    - Bootstrap Seminar Day 3, Sessions 1-4 (4 DVDs), 1990-06-21 (Box 2 (Misc))
    - Bootstrap Seminar Day 1, Sessions 1-4 (4 DVDs), 1992-03-24 (Box 2 (Misc))
    - Bootstrap Seminar Day 2, Sessions 1-4 (4 DVDs), 1992-03-25 (Box 2 (Misc))
    - Bootstrap Seminar Day 3, Sessions 1-3 (3 DVDs), 1992-03-26 (Box 2 (Misc))
    - Bootstrap [Day 1] Sessions 1-4 (4 DVDs), 1991-06-18 (Box 2 (Misc))
    - Bootstrap [Day 2] Sessions 1-4 (4 DVDs), 1991-06-19 (Box 2 (Misc))
    - Bootstrap [Day 3] Sessions 1-4 (4 DVDs), 1991-06-20 (Box 2 (Misc))
    - Engelbart's Unfinished Revolution (4 DVDs), 1999 (Box 2 (Misc))
  - Subseries 3.7. Accession 1988-034. Year of the Pods cassettes (3), circa 1977; 3 audiocassette(s)
- Series 4. Hardware
  - hardware (Flat-box 1 [Hardware))
  - hardware (Flat-box 2 [Hardware))
  - hardware (Flat-box 3 [Hardware))
  - hardware (Flat-box 4 [Hardware))
- Series 5. Accession 1991-191
  - Subseries 5.1. ARC Journals, 1971-1977
    - ARC Journals 7360-7776, June-October 1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 7801-8345, October-December 1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 8347-8565, January 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 8567-8799, January-February 1972 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 8800-9273, February-April 1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 9301-10089, February-April 1972 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 10091-10398, April-May 1972 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 10401-10636, May-June 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 10704-10824, June 1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 10825-11098, June-July 1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 11116-11382, July-August 1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 11406-11899, August-September 1972 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 11900-12068, September-October 1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 12069-12264, October 1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 12326-12558, October-November 1972 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 12573-13015, November 1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 13016-13228, November-December 1972 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 13229-13595, December 1972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 13596-13799, December 1972-January 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 13800-14103, January 1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 14104-14295, January-February 1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 14296-14459, February 1973 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - ARC Journals 14460-14718, February 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 14719-14920, February-March 1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 14921-15125, March 1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 15126-15363, March 1973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 15364-15669, March-April 1973 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 15670-16000, April 1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 16001-16264, April-May 1973 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 16631-16814, May 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 16815-17058, May-June 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 17059-17150, June 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 17151-17438, June-July 1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 17439-17744, June-July 1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 17745-17985, July 1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 18221-18399, August 1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 18400-18629, August 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 16265-16630, May 1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 18630-18785, August 1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 18786-18950, August-September 1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 18951-19070, September 1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 19071-19145, September 1973 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 19146-19301, September 1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 19302-19600, September-October 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - ARC Journals 19601-19871, October 1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - ARC Journals 19872-20200, October-November 1973 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 20201-20500, November 1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 20501-20730, November-December 1973 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 20731-20954, December 1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 20955-21203, December 1973 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 21204-21232, December 1973 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 21233-21517, December 1973-January 1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 21518-21721, January-February 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 21722-21888, February 1974 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 22233-22625, March-April 1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 22626-22778, April 1974 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 22779-22901, April-May 1974 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 22902-23081, May 1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 23082-23188, May 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 23352-23445, June 1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - ARC Journals 23214-23339, June 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 23446-23569, June-July 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 23570-23737, July-August 1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 23738-23895, August 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 23896-23945, August-September 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 23946-24048, September 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 24049-24104, September 1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 24105-24211, September-October 1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - ARC Journals 24105-24295, October 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 24296-24419, October-November 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 24420-24461, November 1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 24462-24578, November 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 24579-24693, November-December 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 24694-24791, December 1974 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 24792-24985, December 1974-March 1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 24986-25104, January 1975 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 25105-25158, January 1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 25159-25247, January 1975 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 25338-25458, February 1975 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 25459-25499, February 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journal 25500-25618 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - ARC Journals 26265-26290, August 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 26391-26486, September 1975 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 26564-26672, September-October 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 25876-25990, May-June 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 26138-26264, July-August 1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 26763-26871, October-November 1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 26989-27099, November-December 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 27100-27199, December 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 27200-27250, December 1975-January 1976 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 27331-27399, January 1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 27400-27485, January-February 1976 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 27486-27599, February 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 27600-27699, February-March 1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 27757-27814, March 1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 27815-27929, April 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - ARC Journals 27930-28004, April-May 1976 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 28200-28370, June-July 1976 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 28472-28509, August 1976 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 28510-28538, August 1976 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 28851-28949, November-December 1976 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 28952-2905, December 1976-January 1977 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 29053-29129, January-February 1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 29186-29232, March-April 1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 29233-29249, April 1977 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 29290-29342, April-May 1977 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - ARC Journals 30000-30158, January-February 1974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - ARC Journals 30159-30300, February-March 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 30301-30443, March-April 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 30444-30540, April 1974 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 30541-30639, April-May 1974 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 30640-30838, May-June 1974 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 30838-30925, June-July 1974 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 30993-31025, August 1974 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 31026-31068, August-September 1974 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - ARC Journals 31069-31100, September 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 31101-31199, September-October 1974 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 31203-31286, November 1974 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 31287-31351, November 1974 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 31353-31451, November-December 1974 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 31452-31541, December 1974 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 31542-31620, December 1974-January 1975 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 31621-31787, January-February 1975 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - ARC Journals 31788-31834, February 1975 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - ARC Journals 31835-31879, February 1975 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - ARC Journals 31880-31885, February 1975 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - ARC Journals 31886-31888, February 1975 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - ARC Journals 31889-31903, February 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 31904-31991, February-March 1975 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 31992-32054, March 1975 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 32056-32135, March 1975 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 32136-32199, March 1975 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 32200-32222, March 1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 32223-32262, March-April 1975 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 32263-32283, April 1975 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - ARC Journals 32284-32307, April 1975 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - ARC Journals 32307-32367, April 1975 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - ARC Journals 32368-32524, April-May 1975 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - ARC Journals 32525-32674, May-June 1975 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - ARC Journals 32675-32762, June 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 32763-32842, June 1975 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 32843-32948, June-July 1975 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 32949-33140, July-August 1975 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 33141-33211, August 1975 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 33212-33300, August 1975 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 33301-33406, August-September 1975 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 33480-33595, September 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 33596-33674, September-October 1975 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 33675-33730, October 1975 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 33731-33868, October-November 1975 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 33869-33915, November 1975 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 33921-33972, November 1975 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 33974-34043, November-December 1975 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 34044-34078, December 1975 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 34079-34130, December 1975 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 34130-34196, December 1975-January 1976 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 34273-34355, January 1976 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 34356-34416, January-February 1976 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 34417-34499, February 1976 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 34501-34599, February 1976 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 34600-34699, February-March 1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 34800-34870, March 1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 34880-34934, April 1976 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 34935-35055, April 1976 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 35056-35181, April 1976 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 35182-35288, April-May 1976 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 35289-35434, May 1976 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 35435-35651, May-June 1976 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 35652-35714, June 1976 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 35715-35867, June 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 35868-35940, June-July 1976 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 35941-36038, July 1976 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 36039-36093, July 1976 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 36094-36188, July 1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 36189-36268, July 1976 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 36270-36388, August 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 36390-36405, August 1976 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 36406-36442, August 1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 36444-36500, August 1976 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 36501-36624, August 1976 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 36624-36705, August-September 1976 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 36706-36794, September 1976 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 36795-36898, September 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 36900-36999, September 1976 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 37000-37097, September-October 1976 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 37100-37232, October 1976 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 37233-37346, October 1976 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 37347-37447, October 1976 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 37448-37569, October-November 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 28615-28699, September 1976 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 37570-37690, November-December 1976 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 37711-37766, November 1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 37767-37799, November 1976 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 37800-37852, November 1976 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 37853-37888, November 1976 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 37889-37999, November-December 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 38000-38092, December 1976 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 38112-38259, December 1976-February 1977 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 38260-38369, December 1976-February 1977 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 38370-38532, January 1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 38534-38649, January 1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journals 38650-38800, January-February 1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - ARC Journals 38801-38931, February 1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 38933-39060, February 1977 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 39160-39299, March 1977 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 39311-39497, March 1977 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 39505-39649, March-April 1977 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 39650-39713, April 1977 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journals 39935-40005, April 1977 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journals 40006-40150, April-May 1977 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journals 40151-40218, May 1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journals 40236-40344, May 1977 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journals 40345-40565, May 1977 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - ARC Journal Catalog Indexes, pre-1972 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - ARC Journal Catalog Indexes, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - ARC Journal Catalog Indexes, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - ARC Journal Catalog Indexes, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - ARC Journal Catalog Indexes Podac Papers -Journal vol. 1, Minutes of POD's (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - ARC Journal Catalog Indexes Podac Papers -Journal vol. 2, POD Dialogue (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 5.2. User Guides
    - Locator-Archive Directories (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Pcopy-Sortkeys (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Archive-Line Processor (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - IMarket-Old Proof (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 5.3. ARC Feedback Journals, 1975-1981
    - ARC Feedback Journals, March-July 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, August-December 1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, January 1976 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, June-September 1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, September 1976-January 1977 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, March-September 1977 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, April-August 1978 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, November-December 1978 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, January-April 1979 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, May-August 1979 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, September-November 1979 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, December 1979-January 1980 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, February-March 1980 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, April-May 1980 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, June-July 1980 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, July-August 1980 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, August-September 1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, September-October 1980 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, October-November 1980 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, November-December 1980 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, December 1980-January 1981 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, January-February 1981 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, February-March 1981 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, March-April 1981 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - ARC Feedback Journals, April-May 1981 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - ARC Feedback Journals Mail Subsystem Development (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - ARC Feedback Journals Mail Subsystem Specs (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - ARC Feedback Journals Transparencies (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - ARC Feedback Journals Various Files on Computers (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - ARC Feedback Journals Transparencies and File Folders on Computers (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - ARC Feedback Journals Network InforMation Center User Guide (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - ARC Feedback Journals Network InforMation Center User Guide, June 1974 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - ARC Feedback Journals Current Catalog of the NIC Collection (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 5.4 Computer Binders, Papers, Notes, Etc.
    - Binders on Computers Frontend, The NlS Backend, Subsystems (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Binders on Computers Frontend, ClI, Subsystems (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Binders on Computers Subsystems, Library to User options (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Computer Binders Calculations and Report Notes (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Computer Binders R-T Dev. Doc. A Burke (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Computer Binders R-T Dev. Doc. B Burke (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Computer Binders NLS10 Subsystems vol. 1 Base-graphics (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Computer Binders FE #2 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Computer Papers Report on Control System Design Study (Box 53)
    - Computer Binders and Notes Computer Systems (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Computer Binders and Notes DCE Office CONS (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Computer Binders and Notes LONS Pre-Draft RFP of a Laboratory Office Network System (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Computer Binders and Notes NSWC Proposal (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Computer Binders and Notes Genisco User's Manual (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Computer Binders and Notes Report Subsystem (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Computer Binders and Notes Telecopy (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Computer Binders and Notes Charges Subsystem (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Computer Binders and Notes User Option Design Notes (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Subsystem Notes NLS Users Notes (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Subsystem Notes USER Guides (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Subsystem Notes Various Other Notes (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Computer Notes (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - DDSI Binder (Box 56)
    - Computer Notes LOCKHEED (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Computer Notes Calendar (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Computer Notes Extensions to Queryz Subsystem: proposal to RADC (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Computer Notes Computer Notes and Papers (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Computer Notes 'ADVANCED' Binder (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Computer Notes Courses Binder (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Computer Notes Training Reports May 1979 to ARC Education Unit/JMB (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Various Notes and Papers (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Weyerhauser Binder (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Various Notes and Papers (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - USER Guides (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Computer Papers Beginning Use of AUGMENT Lesson (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Computer Papers Writing and Reading an Organized File Lesson (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Computer Papers Augment Cue Card Drafts (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Computer Papers Table Lesson Drafts vol. 1 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Computer Papers Command Sequences Final Review (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Computer Papers Table Tutor Drafts (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Computer Papers Augment Mail Users Guide 2nd ed. (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Computer Papers Slides (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Computer Papers Mail Cue Card (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Computer Papers Augment Mail Users' Guide (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Computer Papers Augment Mail Users' Guide 2nd ed. (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Computer Papers Commands Structures and the Process Command (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Computer Papers Advanced Techniques for Display (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Computer Papers Mail Users Guide (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Computer Papers Augment Mail Cue Card (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Computer Papers Augment Mail Users Guide (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Computer Papers Augment Mail Users Guide vol. 3 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Computer Papers Getting Help Lesson (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Computer Papers Operator Procedures (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Computer Papers Beginning Typewriter (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Computer Papers Operator Procedures (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Computer Papers Augment 1250 Users Guide (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Computer Papers Augment 1250 Guide Proofs (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Computer Papers Augment Applications and Features (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Computer Papers Beginning Typewriter Lesson (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Computer Papers Terminal Documents (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Computer Papers Operator's Guide (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Computer Papers Getting Help Lesson (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Computer Papers Table Lesson (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Computer Papers Beginning Typewriter (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Computer Handbooks and Papers (Box 64)
    - Computer Handbooks and Papers (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Computer Binder Tops-20 JSYS Manual (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Computer Binders CompSRC (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Computer Binders Tops-20 Exec (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Computer Binders CoBoL for Tops-20 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Computer Binders NLSBE #1 AdrMnp to Exec Fl (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Computer Binders NLSBE #3 Programs to Verify (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Computer Binders Project Files 4417-4601 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Computer Binders Project Files 4870-4874 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Computer Binders Project Files 750-4871, August-September 1976 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Computer Binders Project Files 5092-5517, May-June 1976 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Computer Binders Project Files 5582-5977 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Computer Binders Project Files 6000-9396, January-March 1977 (Box 67, Folder 6)